Once your virtual mission are ready, the next term we can download the Kali Linux from the
open source platform, so we don't want to pay any kind of any money or anything for Kali
Linux.
So I just included this URL in the resource section, you can find it there and if you
go to the link, you can see a lot of information.
So here you can find virtual mission documentations and pre-built virtual mission.
So click on this, if you are using virtual mission, click on this, if you are using VMware,
go for it.
So based on your requirement, you can download anything.
So at the time, when I was showing this video, it was like the version was 2025.3, so you
can click on this and you can download it.
So once you have downloaded your, you can find it in download folder, then the simple thing
you need to extract the file here.
Already extracted, you need to extract here, I already extracted and it was present here.
So here you can find two files.
So click on this one, okay, virtual box AMD64, the blue color icon.
So once you click on the blue color icon, it has been loaded, it was automatically loaded
inside the virtual box, right?
So you don't need to do any import, export or something, you just click on that and it
will be get exported.
So once you get down to the Kali Linux, then just go to the settings and we can increase
the memory a little bit, increase the memory to like 8GB, based on your customer equipment.
16GB is enough for our course, but so if you have some extra memory, that will be
really, really helpful to do some, okay, and based on your equipment, you can increase
your CPU utilization or processor utilization here, okay.
Then apart from there, you don't need to do any other things, apart from this too.
Now you can start the Kali Linux, okay, so it will take some time to boot up.
Let's see once the Kali Linux was ready.
We need to do some kind of modifications in Kali Linux.
I will show you how to do that.
Our machine gets a boot up.
Let's wait for some more time of the powerful thing from Kali.
So initially your username will be Kali and password will be Kali, okay, username and password
both are Kali Kali, okay.
So the next one, let's expand this, yeah, now it gets expanded, go to terminal, so we can
set a root password, okay, yes, you, sorry, pseudo password, root, okay, this is the command
you need to give, okay.
So now we will be asking for a Kali password, so we know Kali password was Kali and it
was asking to set a new password, okay, so I was sitting the same Kali here.
If you need, you can give other password, so I was sitting a password here, okay.
So now I was switching to root and my password was Kali, okay.
Now I was a root user, right, so also you can switch user mode and you can fill it root
here and you can give the root password.
Now you are switch to root, right, but now the terminal was root, okay.
So this is the initial thing we need to do when you boot some the Kali name, apart from
this, nothing special, you need to do it here, okay, I hope till now we are good with this
and we'll connect you guys in the next video, see you, bye bye.